<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NearEast Hospital</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hospital_info">hospital_info</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us_activity">About US</string>
    <string name="about_us_description_1">
        The Near East University Hospital, as the first and only private university hospital,
        was established as part of planned development projects on campus of the Near East University,
        Lefkosa, North Cyprus. Designed and built with a future-oriented structure and equipped with the latest and most sophisticated medical devices,
        it offers extensive medical services with its highly experienced specialist staff to patients from all over the world.
        The unmatched technology and quality of service offered at the best possible standards can only be obtained from a limited number of most developed western counterparts.
    </string>
    <string name="about_us_description_2">
       North Cyprus is known as a heavenly corner of world with its unique cultural, historical and natural heritage that inspired even the most famous works of Shakespeare
        and Leonardo Da Vinci, and is a well-known touristic destination with all its diverse potentials. The Near East University Nicosia Cyprus is the largest university
        of Cyprus and was established in the heart of Cyprus, the land where traces of the greatest civilizations rose and vanished throughout the history form one of the most
        precious historical and cultural heritage. The development of Near East University, now offering higher education opportunities to undergraduate and postgraduate students
        from over 70 countries, has been continuing in accordance with the internationally realized needs of higher education and of the country. Considering its overall
        responsibilities and potentials as an international foundation, the university also puts its potentials into service of local and international community in many ways
        in order to meet the diverse needs of humanity and support the developments of national and international sectors, including the tourism sector, which is the core sector
        of North Cyprus and hereby supported much by the relevant departments of the university. Healthcare and safety of tourists visiting the other countries is always a
        concern of the tourism sector.
    </string>
     <string name="about_us_description_3">
       In this respect, the Near East University Hospital of NEU was projected as a patient-centered institution and established at the international standards in accordance with
         the criteria set forth by the Joint Comission International (JCI) have been adopted in advance in order to be recognized as a world-class health center offering the best
         possible medical and other relevant services for the patients and tourists coming from abroad. With the establishment of Hospital of Near East University and the Hospital
         of Faculty of Dentistry which is the first private dentistry clinic that obtained the highest grade in evaluation of JCI within the first year of its establishment,
         the concept of medical tourism has been introduced to Cyprus and North Cyprus turned into a healthcare guaranteed tourism destination where the tourists coming to North
         Cyprus from abroad are offered the best possible health services at the international standards.
    </string>
    <string name="about_us_description_4">
       The Hospital of Near East University has a 56,000 square-meter closed area comprising 209 private, single patient rooms, 8 operating theatres, 30-bed Intensive Care Unit,
        17-bed Neonatal Intensive Care Unit, an advanced laboratory where a wide array of medical and experimental tests can be carried out, and a cutting-edge diognostic imaging center,
        and the most advanced Radiotheraphy Centre of the Eastern Mediterranean region equipped with Rapic Arc Technology. The hospital owns fully equipped air-jet ambulance which is also
        the first and only in the region.

    </string>
    <string name="about_us_description_5">
       In consideration with the diverse needs of the international patients, an "International Patient Coordination Center" has also been established to specifically deal with all sort of needs
        of patients coming from abroad. This unit makes all sort of arrangements and meets the medical and social needs of international patients and their companions, providing service in their
        native language. The Centre also arranges tours and social activities within the country. The primary objective of the Centre is to send the patients back to their homes as healthy
        and happy individuals.

    </string>

 <string name="about_us_description_6">
       The Near East University Hospital has been honored with many internationally prestigious awards in 2013 for its quality in terms of service quality, management quality, and dedication
     to values of medicine and humanity. The awards received in 2013 are as follows:

    </string>
     <string name="about_us_description_7">

1.WORLDCOB 2013 Business Excellence Award, Dubai
2.International Socrates Award, Montreaux
3.Best University Golden Award, Montreaux
4.Golden Award For Quality And Business Prestige, Rome
5.2013 Gold Quality Award Of International Arch Of Europe, Frankfurt

    </string>


</resources>
